(大蛇丸)グワ～ッ！
(ヤマト)ナルトが こっちに…。
Naruto is over here...
That thing is not human...
人間業じゃないな…。
Sai, what are you doing?
《サイ… 何をしている》
わかった 監視を続けてくれ。
Got it.
Continue to observe.
Sakura-chan!
((ナルト : サックラちゃ～ん！))
That's... Naruto...
《サクラ : あれが… ナルト…？》
Naruto!
ナルト！
あれは…！
That's...
I can't pierce through...
even with my snake sword...
《この草薙の剣をもってしても
貫けないとはね…》
《自来也様のおっしゃってた➡
This is what Jiraiya-sama
was referring to when he said...
まるで小さな九尾とは
このことか…》
he's "like a small Nine-Tailed Beast".
You are my friend.
you are my friend
Ah that day's dream...
aa ano hi no yume
You haven't forgotten it, have you?
ima demo mada wasuretenain deshou
You are my dream.
you are my dream
Ah it had just started your one longest way.
aa hajimatta bakka kimi no one longest way
Woah, I'm starting on a journey now!
woah ima tabidatsu yo
EVERDAY hereafter is a shining day.
everyday kono saki mo shining day
Unchanging singin', a bright morning smile.
kawarazu singin' hikaru asa no smile
This is the last farewell on funny days.
kore de miosame no funny days
Leaping into the future I see. Go far, dream of my heart.
tobidatsu future mezashita go far kokoro no dream of
I'll go the distance, the endless sky is blue.
i'll go the distance mihatenu sora wa blue
I've hitched a ride on the star ship, this is the best forever trip.
norikonda star ship kore ga saigo no forever trip
You are my friend.
you are my friend
Ah that day's dream...
aa ano hi no yume
You haven't forotten it, have you?
ima demo mada wasuretenai deshou
You are my dream.
you are my dream
Ah, it had just started your one longest way.
aa hajimatta bakka kimi no one longest way
Woah, I'm starting on a journey now!
woah ima tabidatsu yo
Thank you my friend.
thank you my friend
Ah even now,
aa ano hi no koto
I still remember that day.
ima demo mada oboeteru kara
You are my dream.
you are my dream
Ah those days that will never come back.
aa mou nidoto sou modoranai days
Woah I'll go the distance!
woah i'll go the distance
Sakura's Tears
(カブト)これじゃあ
忍者の戦いというより…。
This is not like a Ninja battle,
まるで
バケモノどうしの戦いじゃないか フフッ。
but more like
a battle between monsters...
《ナルト…》
Naruto...
《大蛇丸 : これ以上 草薙の剣で
やり合ってもムダね》
It's useless to go on fighting
with the snake sword...
《サイ : 状況は どうなってる？
What's the situation like?
Is Naruto dead?
ナルトは 死んだのか？》
フフッ…。
Look at that...
見なよ… あれを。
I wonder if he still wants
to save Sasuke-kun...
あんな姿になってまで
サスケ君を助けたかったのかね？
even in that state.
((サスケは絶対 オレが連れて帰る！
I am going to take back Sasuke,
no matter what!
(一生の約束だってばよ！))
It's my lifelong promise!
((サクラちゃん オレ
約束 絶対 守るってばよ！))
Sakura-chan! I... will keep my promise,
no matter what!
((まっすぐ
自分の言葉は曲げねえ！
I stick straight to what I say!
That's my Ninja Way!
(それが オレの忍道だからよ！))
今じゃ 自分の意識すら
とんでしまってる。
By now, even his self-consciousness
is gone...
悲しい子だ…。
What a sad kid...
待て！ サクラ!!
Wait! Sakura!
今のナルトに近づくんじゃない！
Don't get close to Naruto
in that state!
(サクラ)ナルト！
Naruto!
もう… もう いいから！
That's... that's enough!
I will save Sasuke-kun, no matter what!
サスケ君は アタシが助け出してみせる！
だから… ナルトはもう…。
That's why...
Naruto, it's enough...!
《やばい！》
Not good!
《サイ : 何をするつもりだ？》
What is he trying to do?
うっ うぅっ…。
《今がチャンスか…》
Now is my chance...
そろそろ 時間のようね…。
Looks like it's about time...
《大蛇丸 : やっぱり この体じゃ
拒絶反応が 出てしまう…。
As expected,
this body is rejecting me.
残念だけど
遊びは ここまでね…》
Too bad, but the fun ends here.
我慢… 我慢よ…！
Patience... Patience now...
私には サスケ君が いる…。
I have Sasuke-kun with me...
あぁっ…！
あ～あ…。
Oh, uh...
《クソッ！ 間に合わなかったか！》
Damn!
I didn't make it in time...
ううっ…。
ふぅ…。
はぁっ！
手は 出させん！
I won't let you step in.
早とちりだよ。
You're rushing to conclusions.
もう キミたちに
手を 出すつもりはない…。
I don't plan to fight you guys
anymore.
Actually... it's the opposite.
それどころか その逆さ…。
…どういうことだ？
What do you mean?
ボクたちと キミたちには
同じ目的が ある…。
We both have the same goal.
暁が ジャマだ…。
The Akatsuki are in the way.
(カブト)キミたちを 生かしておけば➡
If I let you live...
暁の もう１人くらいは
始末してくれるかもしれないと➡
I think you might
just get rid of one more Akatsuki.
ふと 思ってね…。
《ナルト…》
Naruto...
《傷の治りが
思ったよりも 遅い…。
The wounds are healing
much slower than I expected...
だが いつまでも ボランティアを
やってるわけにもいかないな…》
but I can't stay
playing volunteer for long.
《大蛇丸様も そろそろ時間だ…》
Orochimaru-sama is also
reaching his limit.
助ける代わりに…➡
In exchange for helping you...
please get rid of as many
of the Akatsuki as you can...
暁を １人でも多く
始末してくれ。
(カブト)といっても
あれは キミたちの連れだ…。
That said, that is your teammate...
(カブト)あとは
キミたちで なんとかしなよ。
Take care of the rest.
《引き上げどきだな…》
It's time to leave, huh?
《今しかない！》
Now's the only chance...!
はぁ… はぁ… はぁ…。
I am Danzo-sama's man.
I am not your enemy...
(サイ)ボクは ダンゾウ様の使い。
敵では ありません。
あなたに お話が あります。
I have something
to speak to you about.
火影式耳順術！
Hokage Style: Elder Jutsu
"STABILIZE"
廓庵入鄽垂手！
10th Edict on Enlightenment!
はぁ～っ！
ぐうぅぅ… くっ…。
ナルト…。
Naruto...
ぐぅぅっ… くぅっ…。
ぐっ ぐぅあぁぁぁっ!!
ダンゾウ…。
Danzo... that doddering old fool
is still alive, huh?
あの もうろくじじい…
まだ 生きてたのね。
で… 話って何かしら？
So...
What do you want to talk about?
ダンゾウ様から
大蛇丸様に伝言があります。
I have a message from Danzo-sama
to Orochimaru-sama.
実は…。
(大蛇丸)その前に…。
The truth is...
Before that...
私への言葉は 慎重に選びなさい。
Choose your words carefully
when you talk to me.
でないと 死ぬわよ。
If not, you'll die.
ボクは ダンゾウ様が
おっしゃったとおりにしか➡
I can only relay
what Danzo-sama has told me.
申しあげられません。
それで
お気に召さぬことがあれば➡
If that does not satisfy you,
then I'll leave it up to you...
どうぞ ご自由に…。
ぐあぁっ！
The clouds
drift accross
a distant sky,
The clouds
drift accross
a distant sky,
sora wa haruka
kumo wa nagarete
Far, far, far away,
beyond the horizon.
tooku tooku tooku
ni kogaretemo
Where will I go
from here and
what do I want?
Where will I go
from here and
what do I want?
doko o mezashite boku
wa fumidasu no ka
It's time to break
through my
fears and doubts.
It's time to break
through my
fears and doubts.
mayoi o ima
furikitte
Even though
I have a destiny
that I can't
escape from,
Even though
I have a destiny
that I can't
escape from,
nigeba no nai
unmei demo
I'm searching
for tomorrow.
asu o sagashite
Because the bonds
of friendship
keep me strong.
Because the bonds
of friendship
keep me strong.
boku o tsuyoku
suru no wa
nakama no kizuna
boku o tsuyoku
suru no wa
nakama no kizuna
Awaken the wild
side and let loose
the feelings!
Awaken the wild
side and let loose
the feelings!
mezamero yasei
afuredashita
kanjou
mezamero yasei
afuredashita
kanjou
Hidden within
my heart as I
smile recklessly.
Hidden within
my heart as I
smile recklessly.
mune ni himete
gamushara
no egao de
mune ni himete
gamushara
no egao de
And it's only when
I shout that the
truth is echoed.
And it's only when
I shout that the
truth is echoed.
sakebigoe wa
woah woah
shinjitsu dake
hibiku darou
sakebigoe wa
woah woah
shinjitsu dake
hibiku darou
My heart burns
and I'll hold on
to your hand.
My heart burns
and I'll hold on
to your hand.
kokoro moyase
soshite te o
tsunagou
kokoro moyase
soshite te o
tsunagou
If we're gonna
pursue those
eternal desires.
If we're gonna
pursue those
eternal desires.
yume ni
kometa eien
no negai o
yume ni
kometa eien
no negai o
Your prayer will
be granted,
motomeru nara
woah woah
Because the light
you seek lies there.
sagashiteru
hikari wa kitto
soko ni aru sa
sagashiteru
hikari wa kitto
soko ni aru sa
里を抜けたサスケに代わり
カカシ班に配属された謎の新人 サイ。
絵心に長け
忍法 「超獣偽画」により➡
Awaken the
beast within!
mezamero
yasei
描いた絵を実体化する能力を持つ。
Hmph,
It's you...
At last,
they meet again.
Finally.
Next Episode
一切 感情というものがなく
周囲の空気が読めないため➡
Captain, can you teach me the Jutsu
you used earlier?
That is impossible.
無神経な発言も多い。
Why?
I am the only person in the Leaf Village
who can use that Jutsu...
サイは 「根」と呼ばれる組織に
所属している模様。
because I inherited
the First Hokage Lord's cells.
「根」とは 三代目 火影様と
火影の椅子を巡って争っていた➡
It's always like this...
I can only do little things for Naruto.
The size of the things you do,
big or small, are not important.
タカ派の主導者 ダンゾウによって
作られた 暗部養成所のこと。
What is important is
how you feel about Naruto.
今日 サイが ダンゾウによる極秘任務を
受けている可能性も➡
I can tell by just watching. The truth is, you are...
The Secret of the Battle
Next episode: "The Secret of the Battle!"
否定できない。
でもまぁ ボクの目の黒いうちは➡
I
n
t
e
l
i
g
e
n
c
e
R
p
o
r
t
b
y
t
h
e
A
n
b
u
B
l
a
c
k
O
p
s
Research Report by the Anbu Black Ops.
思いどおりにはさせないよ。
Research Report about Sai.
Sai, the mysterious rookie who was
assigned to Team Kakashi
in place of Sasuke who left the village.
He has artistic talent
and has the power to bring pictures to life
with the Ninja Art: Super Beast Scroll.
He doesn't have any emotions
and because he doesn't
have a sense of situations,
he makes insensitive remarks.
It seems like Sai belongs to
the organization called “The Foundation”.
“The Foundation”
Anbu Black Ops Training Division
was made by Danzo,
head of the hawk side,
who was competing against the
Third Hokage Lord for the Hokage's position.
Today, we cannot eliminate
the possibility that
Sai received a secret mission
from Danzo.
But as long as my eyes are still black...
...I won't let you do as you wish.